Oh, that's a depressing site.
哦 那真是个令人伤心的地方
Hage's been mentally sound for all these years.
哈格这些年的精神状态很好
Then he spends a few months in Tokyo and he's completely lost his mind.
然后他去东京待了几个月 就完全失去了理智
Tokyo's a strange place, Tamasaburo.
东京是个非常奇怪的地方 大阪
I don't understand the people here at all.
我一点都理解不了这里的人
If we would execute Operation Specter on Shikoku Island, it would have worked beautifully
如果我们在四国岛上执行 幽灵行动 会完成得更好
Offerings at our temple would have tripled.
我们寺庙的贡品会有三倍多
Master Kincho, please take me back with you to Shikoku Island,
金鸟大师 求您带我一起回四国岛吧
and train me to follow in your footsteps.
并且训练我跟随您的脚步
There's nothing I would value more.
已经没有什么我会更看重的了
- I see, Tamasaburo. - Yes.
-我知道了 大阪 -在
Do you honestly wish to become my successor?
你真的想成为我的继承者吗
Yes, Master Kincho.
是的 金鸟大师
I've been hoping you would say that.
我一直希望你可以这么说
However, you must assure me
但是 你必须向我保证
that you're not making a selfish decision.
你不会做自私的决定
and abandoning your fellow raccoons just to get back to my daughter.
为了回到我女儿的身边而抛弃你的狸猫伙伴
- Are you? - Of course not, Master.
-你会吗 -当然不会了 大师
- Only. - Only what? Tell me.
-只不过 -只不过什么 告诉我
Even you Master Kincho have lost the support of the other raccoons.
甚至是金鸟大师你都失去了其他狸猫的支持
So what good can we achieve by staying here?
所以我们待在这能有什么好处呢
There is something. Come with me.
有点东西要给你看 跟我来